var myQuestions = [
    {
    number: 1,
    question: "Arrays in JavaScript can be used to store ________.",
    choices: {
        A: 'Numbers and Strings',
        B: 'Other Arrays',
        C: 'Booleans',
        D: 'All of the Above',
    },
    correctAnswer: 'D'
},
    {
    number: 2, 
    question: "String Values must be enclosed with _______ when being assigned to variables.",
    choices: {
        A: 'Commas',
        B: 'Curly Brackets',
        C: 'Quotes', 
        D: 'Parenthesis',
    },
    correctAnswer: 'Quotes',
},
    {
    number: 3, 
    question: "Commonly used data types DO NOT include:",
    choices: {
        A:'Strings',
        B: 'Booleans',
        C: 'Alerts',
        D: 'Numbers',
    },
    correctAnswer: 'Alerts',
},
    {
    number: 4, 
    question: "A very useful tool use during development and debugging for printing content to the debugger is:",
    choices: {
        A: 'JavaScript',
        B: 'Terminal/Bash',
        C: 'For Loops',
        D: 'Console.Log',
    },
    correctAnswer: 'Console.Log',
 },
    {
    number: 5, 
    question: "The condition in an if / else statement is enclosed with ___________. ",
    choices: {
        A: 'Quotes',
        B: 'Curly Brackets',
        C: 'Parenthesis',
        D: 'Square Brackets',
            },
    correctAnswer: 'Parenthesis',
},

    {
    number: 6, 
    question: "Which of the following two CSS properties are used to set an HTML elementâ€™s foreground color and background color, respectively?",
    choices: {
        A: 'Foreground-Color and Background-Color',
        B: 'Color and Background-Color',
        C: 'Color-Foreground and Color-Background',
        D: 'Color-Font and Color-Back',
    correctAnswer: 'Color and Background-Color',
    },
},
    {
    number: 7, 
    question: "What is the correct definition of an HTML element?",
   choices: {
        A: 'The first, or opening, HTML tag',
        B: 'HTML code that does not requir opening or closing tags',
        C: 'An HTML tag adn the content that it contains or marks up',
        D: 'The second, or closing, HTML tag. Closing tags have a forward slash (/) inside of them.',
   },
    correctAnswer: 'An HTML tag and the content that it contains or marks up',
},
    {
    number: 8, 
    question: "What is a directory?",
    choices: {
        A: 'A folder used to store files.',
        B: 'A Tree Structure',
        C: 'A command to a computer',
        D: 'A file',
    },
    correctAnswer: 'A folder used to store files.',
    
},
    {
    number: 9, 
    question: "What does API stand for?",
    choices: {
        A: 'Application Processes Integration',
        B: 'Application Programming Interface',
        C: 'Application Platform Interface',
        D: 'Application Programmer Interface',
    },
    correctAnswer: 'Application Programming Interface',
},
    {
    number: 10, 
    question: "S What does CSS stand for?",
    choices: {
        A: 'Computer Systems Support',
        B: 'Custom Style Sheet',
        C: 'Computer SoftwareServices',
        D: 'Cascading Style Sheet',
    },
    correctAnswer: 'Cascading Style Sheet',
    }
];
